realestateexpress.com 2006-12-29

# Real Estate Express Real Estate License School

This privacy statement covers the Web site www.realestateexpress.com. It is the express goal of American School of Real Estate Express, LLC to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy.

Our postal address is:

American School of Real Estate Express, LLC  
12977 North Forty Drive Suite 214  
St. Louis, MO 63141

We can be reached via e-mail at info@realestateexpress.com

You can reach us by telephone at 866-739-7277.

**Information Collection**

American School of Real Estate Express, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on realestateexpress.com. American School of Real Estate Express, LLC collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Registration  
**

In order to take courses offered on this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information such as name and email address. We use this information to ensure that the user receives credit with state licensing agencies for the continuing education courses completed. American School of Real Estate Express, LLC may also use this information to contact the user about services on our site. In order to take our courses, the user must provide unique identifiers (such as user name and password). A social security number is required, as many states use this as a real estate license number.

**Order  
**

We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name and email) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.  

**Information Use**

The information we collect is used for several purposes. It is used to provide users with confirmation of and proof of credit for the courses taken on Real Estate Express. In many instances information is used to confirm completion of the course(s) with state licensing agencies. The information is also used improve the content of our Web site and to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. 

From time to time, American School of Real Estate Express, LLC uses information volunteered by Web site visitors to deliver email messages regarding special offers on our courses. Each such message contains a clear link to an opt-out utility. All opt-out requests are handled in a timely manner.  
**  
Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. American School of Real Estate Express, LLC sets a single persistent cookie at the time the user registers on realestateexpress.com. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

By allowing American School of Real Estate Express, LLC to set a cookie on users’ computers, users will not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on realestateexpress.com, and will be able to participate in our courses. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The user, however, may be limited in some areas. 

**Log Files  
**Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses and other log file information is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Third Party Advertising**

American School of Real Estate Express, LLC does not permit third party advertising on realestateexpress.com.  

**Information Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Third Party Intermediaries**  
We use a credit card processing company to bill users for American School of Real Estate Express, LLC courses. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Information confirming users’ completion of American School of Real Estate Express, LLC courses is sent to the following states, only for users residing in those states: Alabama, Arizona, Florida, Georgia, Illinois, Iowa, Kansas, Michigan, Missouri, Oklahoma, Tennessee, Virginia and Washington.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event American School of Real Estate Express, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.   

**Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates  
**We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members may occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to opt out of receiving these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their American School of Real Estate Express, LLC account. These communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on an opt-out link in all promotional emails. Users may also unsubscribe from these services, and/or be removed from our database completely, by sending us an email at the addresses provided above, by sending a postal mail at the addresses provided above, or by calling us at the telephone number provided above.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Real Estate Express, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Refer a Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. American School of Real Estate Express, LLC will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. American School of Real Estate Express, LLC stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact American School of Real Estate Express, LLC via email at the addresses provided above, by sending us postal mail at the addresses provided above, or by calling us at the telephone number provided above to request the removal of this information from our database.

**Message Boards, and Public Forums**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – for example on message boards or through e-mail – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ personal information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and transmitted via a secure server. Our secure socket layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

American School of Real Estate Express, LLC also does everything in its power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information – not just the sensitive information mentioned above – is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. On at least an annual basis, and any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure that our users’ information is protected. 

Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [ customercare@realestateexpress.com](mailto:customercare@realestateexpress.com).

**  
Access to Personal Information**

Upon request we provide Web site visitors with access to financial information (e.g., credit card account information) that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them, as well as a full description of information that we maintain about them.  
Consumers can access this information by sending an e-mail to the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, or by writing to us at the above address.   
Upon request we offer Web site users the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, unique identifiers and transaction information.  
Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address. 

**  
Notification of Changes**

If our information practices change at any time, American School of Real Estate Express, LLC will contact users whose personal information we maintain, before we use such data for any new purposes. All such users will be notified of the policy change and provided a clear and convenient opportunity to opt out of the new practices. The personal information of users who do not opt out of the new practices will be subject to the new practices. If users have opted out of all communication with the site, they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. 

Users may also prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending a postal mail to the addresses provided above, or by calling us at the telephone number provided above.

**  
Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at the phone number, email address, or postal address listed at the top of this page.

Since 1997 Real Estate Express has been online offering state-approved real estate courses. We now reach coast to coast with quality, affordable online real estate education. RealEstateExpress.com has become America's Favorite Real Estate School! We offer courses including the California Real Estate License Course, [ Illinois Real Estate License Course](http://www.realestateexpress.com/general/mrepinfo.asp) / [Washington Real Estate License Course](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/WA/prelicense_info.asp) / [Virginia Real Estate License Course](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/VA/prelicense_info.asp) / [Missouri Real Estate License Course ](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/MO/prelicense_info.asp) / [Alabama Real Estate License Course ](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/AL/prelicense_info.asp) / [Kansas Real Estate License Course ](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/KS/prelicense_info.asp) / [Georgia Real Estate License Course](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/GA/prelicense_info.asp) / [Missouri Real Estate Broker License Course](http://www.realestateexpress.com/Broker/MO/broker_info.asp) / [Illinois Real Estate Broker License Course ](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/VA/prelicense_info.asp) / [Iowa Real Estate License Course](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/IA/prelicense_info.asp) / [Florida Real Estate License Course](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/FL/prelicense_info.asp) / [Florida Real Estate License School Packages ](http://www.realestateexpress.com/prelicense/FL/prelicense_info.asp)
